<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: meeting | OKC.js]]></title>
  <link href="http://okcjs.com/blog/categories/meeting/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://okcjs.com/"/>
  <updated>2013-05-15T09:27:53-05:00</updated>
  <id>http://okcjs.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Brightbit]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meeting: August 21 - Double Javascript]]></title>
    <link href="http://okcjs.com/blog/2012/08/17/meeting-august-21-double-javascript/"/>
    <updated>2012-08-17T10:18:00-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://okcjs.com/blog/2012/08/17/meeting-august-21-double-javascript</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="/images/posters/2012-August-21-DoubleJavascript-D3-Frisby.jpg" width="700" title="Double Javascript D3 + FrisbyJs" ></p>

<h2>This Month</h2>

<p>Meeting Tuesday, August 21 at 11:30am at Oklahoma City Metropolitan Library [Ronald J. Norick Downtown</p>

<h3>Spin Kick your Javascript with Frisby.js and Data-Driven Documents[d3]</h3>

<p><img class="float-left rounded-corner-all frisby-js" src="/images/logos/logo-frisby.png" width="250" title="&#34;Double Javascript D3 + FrisbyJs&#34;" alt="&#34;Double Javascript D3 + FrisbyJs&#34;">The first presentation will be on Frisby.js. Frisby is a REST API testing framework built on node.js and Jasmine that makes testing API endpoints easy, fast, and fun.  Frisby.js is invented by Vance Lucas</p>

<p>The second presentation will cover D3. D3 is a avaScript library for manipulating documents based on data. D3 helps you bring data to life using HTML, SVG and CSS. D3's emphasis on web standards gives you the full capabilities of modern browsers without tying yourself to a proprietary framework, combining powerful visualization components and a data-driven approach to DOM manipulation.</p>

<!-- more -->


<h2>About our Speakers</h2>

<h3>Vance Lucas</h3>

<p>Vance Lucas created his first website at the age of 12 and has been focused on web development ever since. Driven to learn more about the web to make better and more interactive websites, Vance taught himself programming with PHP and MySQL back when PHP3 was new at the age of 13. Since PHP5's release, Vance has been focused on and obsessed with object-oriented programming and the advantages it has over the traditional PHP procedural coding style. Vance created the phpDataMapper ORM library as a project to demonstrate the benefits of object-oriented code and the Standard PHP Library (SPL). Vance launched InvoiceMore, an invoicing web application as the flagship product of Actridge, LLC, a company that he founded in February 2009. Vance has recently co-founded a new business called Brightbit doing client work and consulting.</p>

<p><a href="http://twitter.com/vlucas">@vlucas</a></p>

<h3>Jesse Harlin</h3>

<p>Howdy! I am developer at NineCollective who specializes in client side technologies. I am an 'alpha nerd', I love my work, and I am super enthsiastic about things like Javascript, Html/Css and Unity 3D. I've been working in the web for nearly a decade, and am especially excited about the incredible attention javascript has recieved lately as a programming language. When I am not programming at work I am probably programming at home. I love using code to write algorithmic music, program robots, automate Blender, create new electronic musical instruments, and make interactive media. When I am not doing that, I am working to help enrich the programming usergroup communities, both by participating and leading.</p>

<p><a href="http://twitter.com/5imian">@5imian</a></p>

<h2>Tasty Lunch!</h2>

<p>Tasty lunch will be served thanks to <a href="http://www.roberthalftechnology.com/">Robert Half Technologies</a>. These awesome folks are passionate about serving the Oklahoma City technology community and we thank them for their generous support. They've made it clear they want to see our usergroup succeed, which is an epic win for everyone!</p>

<h2>usergroup.location = OKC Metropolitan Library;</h2>

<p><img class="float-left rounded-corner-all metro-library" src="/images/logos/metro-cybermars.png" width="250" title="&#34;Double Javascript D3 + FrisbyJs&#34;" alt="&#34;Double Javascript D3 + FrisbyJs&#34;"></p>

<p><a href="http://www.mls.lib.ok.us/">Oklahoma City Metropolitan Library</a> [Ronald J. Norick Downtown Library]</p>

<p>Meeting Room 46th Star Auditorium, on the 4th Floor.</p>

<p>300 Park Avenue,
Oklahoma City, Ok 73102</p>

<p>405.606.3728</p>

<p><a href="https://maps.google.com/maps?q=Oklahoma+City+Metropolitan+Library+300+Park+Avenue,+Oklahoma+City,+Ok+73102+405.606.3728&amp;hl=en&amp;sll=35.309049,-98.716558&amp;sspn=8.907145,7.218018&amp;hq=Oklahoma+City+Metropolitan+Library+300+Park+Avenue,+Oklahoma+City,+Ok+73102+405.606.3728&amp;t=m&amp;z=7">Google maps link</a></p>

<p><a href="http://www.mls.lib.ok.us/mls/mls_library/dn_parking.pdf">Parking Locations</a></p>

<p>Parking will be the most difficult part of meeting at the library, so you should know there are 7 nearby locations you can use. The locations are marked in the link above in a map. there is
Sheridan Walker Garage, Central parking on Hudson, across from that is Metro Parking.
Around the corner is Century Garage, and Cox Parking Garage at the intersection of Robinson and Sheridan
After you've parked, make your way to the fourth floor of the library and find room 46, the Star Auditorium.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meeting: July 17 - Processing.js]]></title>
    <link href="http://okcjs.com/blog/2012/07/16/meeting-july-17-processing-dot-js/"/>
    <updated>2012-07-16T11:29:00-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://okcjs.com/blog/2012/07/16/meeting-july-17-processing-dot-js</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="/images/posters/2012-july-17-processingjs.jpeg" width="700" title="Processing.js" ></p>

<h2>This Month: Heads Up! Location Change!</h2>

<p>The Div was an awesome place to hold our meetings for a long time. The Div is evolving now, and <a href="http://thediv.org/2012/06/18/our-new-focus-and-pivot/">shifting its focus to better serve the Oklahoma Tech Community</a>. Since they are focusing on inspiring a new generation of developers, their facility this month will be used to host a Scratch Camp, and in the future they will focus more on <a href="http://thediv.org/div-jr-program/">Div Jr</a>.</p>

<p>We are thankful for the awesome time we spent there! However, now we
need to meet at a differnt location, so for this month we are going to
meet at <a href="http://www.metrotech.edu/campuses/edc.html">MetroTech Economic Development Center</a> in <strong>Room 114</strong> (<a href="http://goo.gl/maps/2L30">view map</a>). For this building on campus you should park in Lot I, and the entrance is either entry 13 or 14.</p>

<p>Here are some maps to help you find us:<br/>
 * <a href="http://goo.gl/maps/3uo6">How to get to Metro Tech Springlake Campus</a><br/>
 * <a href="http://www.metrotech.edu/campuses/springlakemap.pdf">A Map of the Springlake Campus (pdf)</a></p>

<h3>Its time to take your visualization capabilities to the next level</h3>

<p><a href="http://processingjs.org">Processing.js</a> is the sister project of the popular Processing visual programming language, designed for the web. Processing.js makes your data visualizations, digital art, interactive animations, educational graphs, video games, etc. work using web standards and without any plug-ins. You write code using the Processing language, include it in your web page, and Processing.js does the rest. It's not magic, but almost.</p>

<p>Yury is going to help us get started with Processing.js. There is a reason Processing is highly popular with lots of creative people. Processing.js brings the best of visual programming to the web, both for Processing and web developers.   Processing can help you achieve practical goals, but it can also be a means for self expression. If you've been amazed at some of the cool things happening in the browser, and are interested in being a part of the exciting changes javascript is bringing to modern development; don't miss this meeting!</p>

<!-- more -->


<h2>About our Speakers</h2>

<h3>Yury Delendik</h3>

<p>Yury Delendik’s first open source project was the processing.js. Since then, he is involved with the Mozilla community. He likes to implement various binary formats decoders in JavaScript and other languages. Currently, he works at Mozilla Research on the <a href="http://andreasgal.com/2011/06/15/pdf-js/">pdf.js</a> and <a href="https://github.com/mozilla/shumway">shumway</a> projects.</p>

<p><a href="https://github.com/yurydelendik">Check out Yury on GitHub!</a></p>

<h2>Tasty Lunch!</h2>

<p>Tasty lunch will be served thanks to <a href="http://www.roberthalftechnology.com/">Robert Half Technologies</a>. These awesome folks are passionate about serving the Oklahoma City technology community and we thank them for their generous support. They've made it clear they want to see our usergroup succeed, which is an epic win for everyone!</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meeting: May 15 - Knock-Out! Your Browser!]]></title>
    <link href="http://okcjs.com/blog/2012/05/14/meeting-may-15-knock-out-your-browser/"/>
    <updated>2012-05-14T09:41:00-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://okcjs.com/blog/2012/05/14/meeting-may-15-knock-out-your-browser</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="/images/posters/2012-may-15-knockout.jpg" width="700" title="Knock-Out! Your Browser!" ></p>

<h2>This Month</h2>

<p>Meeting May 15, 2012 from 11:30am - 12:30pm at <a href="http://thediv.org">the &lt;div&gt;</a> in Edmond, OK. Lunch will be provided!</p>

<h3>Knock-Out!! Your Browser</h3>

<p>This month we have a story of true victory. Users expect a modern web application to be a responsive and rich interactive experience. Users will be accessing your site from a variety of mediums, and will be expecting immediate feedback when they are interacting with the page. Don't let this send a haymaker to your appliation!</p>

<p>This month we have two presentations lined up to get your browser down to fighting weight. In one corner we have Micah Choquette, who will teach you how to adapt your application to any viewing environment. You can 'Parry and Block' and 'Slip and Turn', as a whole host of viewing resolutions and devices get thrown at your app. In the other corner, we have Michael Sarchet who will teach you how to create a highly interactive experince with knockout.js. Use the power of MVVM to Cross, Hook and Jab your clientside viewmodel. Your pages will float like a butterfly and sting like a bee!</p>

<p>Its time to weigh in. The browser is waiting for your challenge!!</p>

<!-- more -->


<h2>About our Speakers</h2>

<h3>Micah Choquette</h3>

<p>A freelance web designer since 2003, Micah was hired on at the Tulsa World in 2010 to help launch their very successful Metered Model. His passion is working with small and micro-businesses and helping them rediscover and communicate their core values to their audience on the web. He believes in doing work that matters.</p>

<p><a href="http://twitter.com/meetmicah">@meetmicah</a> - <a href="http://www.meetmicah.com/">Check Out Micah's Website</a></p>

<h3>Michael Sarchet</h3>

<p>Michael has been programming ever since he started learning QBasic at
the age of 11 on his 486dx. He currently works in C# for his job, and
enjoys working in Ruby/Rails/etc</p>

<p><a href="http://twitter.com/msarchet">@msarchet</a></p>

<h2>Tasty Lunch!</h2>

<p>Tasty lunch will be served thanks to <a href="http://www.roberthalftechnology.com/">Robert Half Technologies</a>. These awesome folks are passionate about serving the Oklahoma City technology community and we thank them for their generous support. They've made it clear they want to see our usergroup succeed, which is an epic win for everyone!</p>

<h2>usergroup.location = theDiv</h2>

<p>With the okcCoCo undergoing change, we will be moving our meetup location to <a href="http://thediv.org">the &lt;div&gt;</a> in Edmond this month. The &lt;div&gt; is an organization who is dedicated to supporting a grassroots usergroup movement that builds the state, and helps champion Oklahoma as a web tech hub. The div is located at <em>1712 S. Kelly Ave, in Edmond</em>. We are really excited to be here this month, and offer our sincere thanks to the div for helping us.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meeting: March 20 - jQuery UI and Photoshop Automation]]></title>
    <link href="http://okcjs.com/blog/2012/03/19/meeting-march-20-jquery-ui-and-photoshop-automation/"/>
    <updated>2012-03-19T10:23:00-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://okcjs.com/blog/2012/03/19/meeting-march-20-jquery-ui-and-photoshop-automation</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="/images/posters/2012-march-20-frontend.jpg" width="700" title="jQuery UI and Photoshop Automation" ></p>

<h2>About "Ninjas of the Javascript"</h2>

<p>Meeting March 20, 2012 from 11:30am - 12:30pm at <a href="http://thediv.org">the &lt;div&gt;</a> in Edmond, OK. Batteries not included, but lunch is!</p>

<h3>A Frontal Assault</h3>

<p>Last month, we highlighted some of the awesome things happening with
serverside javascript. Now,  this month we want to highlight some
awesome uses of javascript for the client, and for frontend designers.
We have two awesome presentations lined up that will demonstrate the
diversity and usefulness of javascript in your workflow.</p>

<h3>Photoshop Automation With Javascript</h3>

<p>Javascript is everwhere, and if you frequently work in programs such as
image editors, video editors and sound editors you might be surprised to
find Javascript in the most unlikely of places. That means as a
developer or designer, harnessing the power of scripting gives you an
incredible edge. Photoshop gives you the ability to implement javascript
for a variety of tasks, which can save you time. It is time to learn the
ancient secrets of Photoshop, and Dragon Punch™ your photoshop workflow
with the power of Javascript.</p>

<h3>Effective Clientside Patterns with the jQuery UI Widget factory</h3>

<p>Many of you use jQuery, and similarly, many of you use jQuery UI. Its
time to go beyond simply using the presets and default widgets in your
jQuery UI library. In this talk, we will cover how $.widget really
works, and how beyond its surface, using the widget factory can help you
write elegant and well organized javascript code in your next
application. Do not attend expecting a blow by blow demonstration of the
default widgets. Instead, this is for those who are looking for ways to
organize their codebase with good patterns and solve their own unique
problems with jQuery UI.  Shadow Kick™ your web application's clientside
codebase with the awesome javascript conventions, CSS conventions and
state management afforded by jQuery UI!</p>

<!-- more -->


<h2>About our Speakers</h2>

<h3>Eric Granata</h3>

<p>Hello, I'm Eric Granata and I am a visual communicator working in
graphic design, web design, video production and motion graphics. For
the past 8 years I have specialized in creative work for churches and
non-profits. I'm a blogger, entrepeneuer, designer and developer.
I get juiced about small business and start-ups and would love to see
that you are up to and help if I can.</p>

<p><a href="http://twitter.com/granta">@granta</a> - <a href="http://ericgranata.com">Eric's Website</a></p>

<h3>Jesse Harlin</h3>

<p>Howdy! I  am developer at <a href="http://www.ninecollective.com">NineCollective</a>  who specializes in client side
technologies. I am an 'alpha nerd',  I love my work, and I am super
enthsiastic about things like Javascript, Html/Css and Unity 3D. I've
been working in the web for nearly a decade, and am especially excited
about the incredible attention javascript has recieved lately as a
programming language. When I am not programming at work I am probably
programming at home. I love using code to write algorithmic music,
program robots, automate Blender, create new electronic musical
instruments, and make interactive media. When I am not doing that, I am
working to help enrich the programming usergroup communities, both by
participating and leading.</p>

<p><a href="http://twitter.com/5imian">@5imian</a></p>

<h2>Tasty Lunch!</h2>

<p>This month we are extremely lucky to be sponsored by <a href="http://www.gdhconsulting.com/">GDH Consulting</a>. GDH
is a specializeed consulting and resource firm focused on providing
qualified professionals within the Information Technology,
telecommunication and Consulting industries to commercial and government
sectors. GDH is a strong supporter of local usergroups and developers,
and is very active in the programming community. We are sincerely
grateful they are providing lunch for us.</p>

<h2>usergroup.location = theDiv</h2>

<p>With the okcCoCo undergoing change, we will be moving our meetup location
to <a href="http://thediv.org">the &lt;div&gt;</a> in Edmond this month. The &lt;div&gt; is an organization who is dedicated to
supporting a grassroots usergroup movement that builds the state, and
helps champion Oklahoma as a web tech hub. The div is located at <em>1712 S. Kelly Ave, in Edmond</em>. We are really excited to be here this month, and
offer our sincere thanks to the div for helping us.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meeting: Feb. 21 - Node.js and Socket.io]]></title>
    <link href="http://okcjs.com/blog/2012/02/14/meeting-feb-21-node-dot-js-and-socket-dot-io/"/>
    <updated>2012-02-14T17:14:00-06:00</updated>
    <id>http://okcjs.com/blog/2012/02/14/meeting-feb-21-node-dot-js-and-socket-dot-io</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="/images/posters/2012-feb-21-node.jpg" width="700" title="Node.js and Socket.io" ></p>

<h2>Rock Your World with Node.js and Socket.io!</h2>

<p>We already have a robust usergroup in terms of size, and we are attempting something ambitious - a live coding session with audience participation. We will have two speakers at our coding session, Ben Van Treese, and Rob Sullivan. Bring your laptops to the meeting if you want to participate and be blown away by live websocket awesomeness.</p>

<p>First, Ben is going to help you go full throttle from neophyte to awesome in the exciting world of Node. We are going to first cover the basics of node and then construct a small node app for the first part of the meeting. This should be a perfect entry point for those new to node, but should also be practical for those at a novice skill level. Then we will cover some more advanced material. Rob is going to join in and simulate an Enterprise environment and load for our app. Everyone interested in Node.js, websockets, and real-time communications should get something out of this presentation.</p>

<!-- more -->


<h2>About our Speakers</h2>

<h3>Rob Sullivan</h3>

<p>Rob is a bona fide Alpha Nerd, SQL Server DBA by day and code slinger by night. He is also the token DBA on This Developers Life, SQL Dude for Tekpub, open source contributor to .NET Micro ORMS and speaker. He is an active member of the Oklahoma City Developers Group and founder/officer of his beloved Oklahoma City SQL Server Developers Group.</p>

<p><a href="http://twitter.com/datachomp">@datachomp</a> - <a href="http://datachomp.com/">Check out Rob's blog!</a></p>

<h3>Ben Van Tresse</h3>

<p>Ben Van Treese is a developer at Nine Collective focusing on server side and client side programming. Ben is a graduate of Southwestern Oklahoma State University with a B.S. in Computer Science. He has been programming for over 10 years in various programming languages. Ben's other interests include everything from cooking and gardening to machine learning and robotics.</p>

<p><a href="http://twitter.com/vantreeseba">@vantreeseba</a> - <a href="https://github.com/vantreeseba">See what Ben is doing on GitHub!</a></p>

<h2>Lunch!</h2>

<p>We learned last month that the same demographic that writes javascript apparently is also the same demographic that can totally vaporize pizza. That or we underestimated just how awesome our turnout would be. In any case we are prepared this February. Tasty lunch will be served for those who attend, but don't thank us - thank <a href="http://www.principaltechnologies.com/">Principal Technologies</a>. These awesome folks are passionate about serving the Oklahoma City technology community, and we thank them for providing lunch, and helping support us.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
