<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: meeting | OKC.js]]></title>
  <link href="http://okcjs.com/blog/categories/meeting/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://okcjs.com/"/>
  <updated>2012-04-03T11:55:53-05:00</updated>
  <id>http://okcjs.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Brightbit]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meeting: March 20 - jQuery UI and Photoshop Automation]]></title>
    <link href="http://okcjs.com/blog/2012/03/19/meeting-march-20-jquery-ui-and-photoshop-automation/"/>
    <updated>2012-03-19T10:23:00-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://okcjs.com/blog/2012/03/19/meeting-march-20-jquery-ui-and-photoshop-automation</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="/images/posters/2012-march-20-frontend.jpg" width="700" title="jQuery UI and Photoshop Automation" ></p>

<h2>About "Ninjas of the Javascript"</h2>

<p>Meeting March 20, 2012 from 11:30am - 12:30pm at <a href="http://thediv.org">the &lt;div&gt;</a> in Edmond, OK. Batteries not included, but lunch is!</p>

<h3>A Frontal Assault</h3>

<p>Last month, we highlighted some of the awesome things happening with
serverside javascript. Now,  this month we want to highlight some
awesome uses of javascript for the client, and for frontend designers.
We have two awesome presentations lined up that will demonstrate the
diversity and usefulness of javascript in your workflow.</p>

<h3>Photoshop Automation With Javascript</h3>

<p>Javascript is everwhere, and if you frequently work in programs such as
image editors, video editors and sound editors you might be surprised to
find Javascript in the most unlikely of places. That means as a
developer or designer, harnessing the power of scripting gives you an
incredible edge. Photoshop gives you the ability to implement javascript
for a variety of tasks, which can save you time. It is time to learn the
ancient secrets of Photoshop, and Dragon Punch™ your photoshop workflow
with the power of Javascript.</p>

<h3>Effective Clientside Patterns with the jQuery UI Widget factory</h3>

<p>Many of you use jQuery, and similarly, many of you use jQuery UI. Its
time to go beyond simply using the presets and default widgets in your
jQuery UI library. In this talk, we will cover how $.widget really
works, and how beyond its surface, using the widget factory can help you
write elegant and well organized javascript code in your next
application. Do not attend expecting a blow by blow demonstration of the
default widgets. Instead, this is for those who are looking for ways to
organize their codebase with good patterns and solve their own unique
problems with jQuery UI.  Shadow Kick™ your web application's clientside
codebase with the awesome javascript conventions, CSS conventions and
state management afforded by jQuery UI!</p>

<!-- more -->


<h2>About our Speakers</h2>

<h3>Eric Granata</h3>

<p>Hello, I'm Eric Granata and I am a visual communicator working in
graphic design, web design, video production and motion graphics. For
the past 8 years I have specialized in creative work for churches and
non-profits. I'm a blogger, entrepeneuer, designer and developer.
I get juiced about small business and start-ups and would love to see
that you are up to and help if I can.</p>

<p><a href="http://twitter.com/granta">@granta</a> - <a href="http://ericgranata.com">Eric's Website</a></p>

<h3>Jesse Harlin</h3>

<p>Howdy! I  am developer at <a href="http://www.ninecollective.com">NineCollective</a>  who specializes in client side
technologies. I am an 'alpha nerd',  I love my work, and I am super
enthsiastic about things like Javascript, Html/Css and Unity 3D. I've
been working in the web for nearly a decade, and am especially excited
about the incredible attention javascript has recieved lately as a
programming language. When I am not programming at work I am probably
programming at home. I love using code to write algorithmic music,
program robots, automate Blender, create new electronic musical
instruments, and make interactive media. When I am not doing that, I am
working to help enrich the programming usergroup communities, both by
participating and leading.</p>

<p><a href="http://twitter.com/5imian">@5imian</a></p>

<h2>Tasty Lunch!</h2>

<p>This month we are extremely lucky to be sponsored by <a href="http://www.gdhconsulting.com/">GDH Consulting</a>. GDH
is a specializeed consulting and resource firm focused on providing
qualified professionals within the Information Technology,
telecommunication and Consulting industries to commercial and government
sectors. GDH is a strong supporter of local usergroups and developers,
and is very active in the programming community. We are sincerely
grateful they are providing lunch for us.</p>

<h2>usergroup.location = theDiv</h2>

<p>With the okcCoCo undergoing change, we will be moving our meetup location
to <a href="http://thediv.org">the &lt;div&gt;</a> in Edmond this month. The &lt;div&gt; is an organization who is dedicated to
supporting a grassroots usergroup movement that builds the state, and
helps champion Oklahoma as a web tech hub. The div is located at <em>1712 S. Kelly Ave, in Edmond</em>. We are really excited to be here this month, and
offer our sincere thanks to the div for helping us.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meeting: Feb. 21 - Node.js and Socket.io]]></title>
    <link href="http://okcjs.com/blog/2012/02/14/meeting-feb-21-node-dot-js-and-socket-dot-io/"/>
    <updated>2012-02-14T17:14:00-06:00</updated>
    <id>http://okcjs.com/blog/2012/02/14/meeting-feb-21-node-dot-js-and-socket-dot-io</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="/images/posters/2012-feb-21-node.jpg" width="700" title="Node.js and Socket.io" ></p>

<h2>Rock Your World with Node.js and Socket.io!</h2>

<p>We already have a robust usergroup in terms of size, and we are attempting something ambitious - a live coding session with audience participation. We will have two speakers at our coding session, Ben Van Treese, and Rob Sullivan. Bring your laptops to the meeting if you want to participate and be blown away by live websocket awesomeness.</p>

<p>First, Ben is going to help you go full throttle from neophyte to awesome in the exciting world of Node. We are going to first cover the basics of node and then construct a small node app for the first part of the meeting. This should be a perfect entry point for those new to node, but should also be practical for those at a novice skill level. Then we will cover some more advanced material. Rob is going to join in and simulate an Enterprise environment and load for our app. Everyone interested in Node.js, websockets, and real-time communications should get something out of this presentation.</p>

<!-- more -->


<h2>About our Speakers</h2>

<h3>Rob Sullivan</h3>

<p>Rob is a bona fide Alpha Nerd, SQL Server DBA by day and code slinger by night. He is also the token DBA on This Developers Life, SQL Dude for Tekpub, open source contributor to .NET Micro ORMS and speaker. He is an active member of the Oklahoma City Developers Group and founder/officer of his beloved Oklahoma City SQL Server Developers Group.</p>

<p><a href="http://twitter.com/datachomp">@datachomp</a> - <a href="http://datachomp.com/">Check out Rob's blog!</a></p>

<h3>Ben Van Tresse</h3>

<p>Ben Van Treese is a developer at Nine Collective focusing on server side and client side programming. Ben is a graduate of Southwestern Oklahoma State University with a B.S. in Computer Science. He has been programming for over 10 years in various programming languages. Ben's other interests include everything from cooking and gardening to machine learning and robotics.</p>

<p><a href="http://twitter.com/vantreeseba">@vantreeseba</a> - <a href="https://github.com/vantreeseba">See what Ben is doing on GitHub!</a></p>

<h2>Lunch!</h2>

<p>We learned last month that the same demographic that writes javascript apparently is also the same demographic that can totally vaporize pizza. That or we underestimated just how awesome our turnout would be. In any case we are prepared this February. Tasty lunch will be served for those who attend, but don't thank us - thank <a href="http://www.principaltechnologies.com/">Principal Technologies</a>. These awesome folks are passionate about serving the Oklahoma City technology community, and we thank them for providing lunch, and helping support us.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[First Meeting: January 2012]]></title>
    <link href="http://okcjs.com/blog/2012/01/03/first-meeting-january-2012/"/>
    <updated>2012-01-03T10:38:00-06:00</updated>
    <id>http://okcjs.com/blog/2012/01/03/first-meeting-january-2012</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>The inagural OKC.js meeting will be on Tuesday, January 24th from 11:30-12:30 at the <a href="http://okccoco.com">okcCoCo</a> in Midtown OKC.</p>

<p><a href="http://www.vancelucas.com">Vance Lucas</a> will give a short presentation on JavaScript BDD testing with <a href="http://pivotal.github.com/jasmine/">Jasmine</a>, followed by a group discussion about what people want from the group, topics people want to hear or present on, and the direction of the group in the future.</p>

<p>This group will be open and benifical to anyone involved in any form of JavaScript at any level. We will cover front-end topics like <a href="http://jquery.com">jQuery</a>, HTML5 APIs and the DOM, back-end development topics with tools like <a href="http://nodejs.org">Node.js</a>, <a href="http://expressjs.com/">Express</a>, and <a href="http://npmjs.org/">NPM</a>, as well as core JavaScript fundamentals like proper namespacing and the <a href="http://www.adequatelygood.com/2010/3/JavaScript-Module-Pattern-In-Depth">module pattern</a>.</p>

<p>Lunch and drinks will be provided by the nice folks at <a href="http://ninecollective.com/">Nine Collective</a>, so come have a free lunch and get involved in the local JavaScript community.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
