<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Kyle Simpson | OKC.js]]></title>
  <link href="http://okcjs.com/blog/categories/kyle-simpson/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://okcjs.com/"/>
  <updated>2014-06-11T00:03:57+00:00</updated>
  <id>http://okcjs.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Brightbit]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meeting: Sept 17 - New Rules of Javascript]]></title>
    <link href="http://okcjs.com/blog/2013/08/20/sept-meeting-new-rules-of-js+copy/"/>
    <updated>2013-08-20T11:30:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://okcjs.com/blog/2013/08/20/sept-meeting-new-rules-of-js copy</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>{% img /images/posters/2013-sept-new-rules-of-js.jpg 700 Kyle Simpson %}</p>

<h2>This Month</h2>

<p>Tuesday: Sept 17, 2013</p>

<p>11:30 am</p>

<p>@The Exchange
700 1/2 W. Sheridan Ave.,
Oklahoma City, Oklahoma
73102</p>

<h2>"About "The New Rules For Javascript"</h2>

<p>I bet you've been writing JS for years and you think you're pretty good at it. I bet you think you know all about how functions create closured scope, and how <code>this</code> gets bound, and even how <code>.prototype</code> works. Or, rather, you probably don't care because your framework or library takes care of all that for you.</p>

<p>JavaScript is generally considered one of the most misunderstood (and maligned) languages of the modern programming era. And there's good reason for that, because most developers who write JS never actually deeply <em>know</em> how the language works. They blame all their WTFs on language bugs, instead of the shortcomings in understanding.</p>

<p>This talk re-visits some of the "tough parts" of the language by declaring "New Rules"</p>

<!-- more -->


<h2>About our Speakers</h2>

<h3>Kyle Simpson</h3>

<h4><a href="http://getify.me/">@getify</a></h4>

<p>Kyle Simpson is an Open Web Evangelist from Austin, TX. He's passionate about JavaScript, HTML5, real-time/peer-to-peer communications, and web performance. Otherwise, he's probably bored by it. Kyle is an author, workshop trainer, tech speaker, and avid OSS community member.</p>

<h3>Our Sponsors</h3>

<p>Tasty lunch will be served thanks to <a href="http://www.roberthalftechnology.com/">Robert Half Technologies</a>. These awesome folks are passionate about serving the Oklahoma City technology community and we thank them for their generous support. They've made it clear they want to see our usergroup succeed, which is an epic win for everyone!</p>

<h2>usergroup.location = The Exchange;</h2>

<p><a href="http://www.exchangeokc.com/">The Exchange</a></p>

<p>The Exchange is located on the second floor of the historic Film Exchange building in downtown Oklahoma City.  This unique loft space is a breath of fresh air for those wanting to step away from traditional event locals and reception areas while still remaining close to all the action of the city.</p>

<p>The Exchange
700 1/2 West Sheridan Avenue
Oklahoma City, OK 73102</p>

<p>(405) 601-9200</p>

<p><a href="https://maps.google.com/maps?q=+700+West+Sheridan+Avenue+Oklahoma+City,+OK+73102&amp;hl=en&amp;sll=37.0625,-95.677068&amp;sspn=83.75977,57.919922&amp;hnear=700+W+Sheridan+Ave,+Oklahoma+City,+Oklahoma+73102&amp;t=m&amp;z=17">Google maps link</a></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
